ticketluck.com 2012-06-09

# Policies: Ticket Luck

For Less Corp. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions.   
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Sara Jones at [sara@ticketluck.com](mailto:sara@ticketluck.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).   
For Less Corp. is firmly committed to protecting your privacy while you are visiting our Web site. The following Privacy Policy discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for [www.TicketLuck.com](http://www.ticketluck.com/)

**INFORMATION THIS SITE GATHERS/TRACKS**   
We use your IP address and browser type to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. This means that your session is never associated with any of your personal information.   
The Contact Us form has the following mandatory fields:

  1. Name: This is used to address the person, seeking to contact us.
  2. E-Mail: This is used to respond to the person, seeking to contact us.
  3. Verification Code: This is an auto generated number to prevent automated programs such as web robots to spam us.
  4. Query: This is the body of the text.

The contact form also has the following optional fields which are used to facilitate communication, should the person feel it’s necessary. These fields are:  
Address, Telephone & Fax and Company name.  
All mandatory fields are denoted with an asterisk(*).

**CORRECTING/UPDATING INFORMATION**  
We never store any information after responding to your email and therefore it is not possible for you to update the information. If your contact information has changed, you will have to resubmit the contact information.  
**_Security_**  
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.   
**_  
Changes to this privacy policy_**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage prior to the changes taking effect.

**  “Purchasing tickets”-**  
When purchasing tickets we direct you to our third party ticket provider's site to complete the purchase process.  You are providing your personal information such as name address, and credit card number to that third party directly.   In some cases the pages may be framed so it appears you are still on our web site to provide you a seamless purchase process.   In these cases you are actually on our third party ticket provider's web site and your information is being collected by that site.   
The information collected on these sites is governed by their privacy policies and we encourage you to read their posted privacy policy.  
**  
 Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**   
We use Third Party Service Providers to assist us in analyzing the aggregate information about the visitors on our site. This information, which helps us optimize the usability of our site, is collected via Service Provider cookie or log files. We do not link any aggregate information to PII. 

**Cookies**   
We use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart, customize your future shopping, and to assist your needs. These are java script based first party cookies and are unable to link to personally identifiable information (PII). Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.  We have no access to or control over these cookies.   
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Our third party web analytics partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our sites by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

**LINKS**   
This site contains links to other sites. This site is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to read posted privacy statements whenever interacting with any Web site. We will not share any specific information that you provide to us without your explicit permission to share it. We may share broad demographic information with others. We will never release your personal information (including but not limited to your name, email address, street address, and phone number) without your express permission. 

_Customer Service Emails_

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us we will communicate with you in response to your inquiries or to provide the services you request. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. If you do not wish to receive emails from us please do not submit any.  
****  
Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information.  For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [sara@ticketluck.com](mailto:sara@ticketluck.com)

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

Change in Ownership  
If For Less Corp. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.  
**CONTACT US**   
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the security practices of this site, please contact us through one of the methods listed on the contact us page of our site   
Or 

Customer Care at [sara@ticketluck.com](mailto:sara@ticketluck.com), or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

For Less Corp.  
4010 Crescent Point,  
Carlsbad, CA 92008   
**_Legal Disclaimer_** ****  
_We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site_
